>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我总结一下双方面的工作。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let me summarize
how double equals works.
这是算法的摘要，您可以读取算法，但它是摘要。
This is summary of the algorithm, you
can read the algorithm but it's summary.
如果相同类型的类型要使用三重对等项。
If the types of the same it's
just gonna use triple equals.
如果两者中的任何一个都是 " 否 " 或 " 未定义 " ，那么它们是相等的。
If either of them both of them are no or
undefined, they are equal.
如果比较中涉及非原语，
If there are non primitives
involved in the comparison,
他们总是先有先人
they are always gonna
become primitive first.
一旦你有了基本的选择
And then once you have
primitives prefer to number.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我对每个开发者都很乐观
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And I'm just optimistic
enough to believe that every developer
有两个星期的 JavaScript经历
from the junior developer with two
weeks of experience in JavaScript,
向经验丰富的开发人员提供了二十几年的时间
up to the experienced
developer with 20 plus years,
能理解一个相当直率的系统
can understand a fairly
straightforward system like that.
通过理解，避免出现问题的地方。
And by understanding it, avoid
the places where it can be problematic.
>> Kyle Simpson: 那么有问题的案例是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
what are those problematic cases?
其中很多是我们已经见过的，但是我们要谈的是转角的情况，
Many of these are ones we've already seen,
but let's talk about the corner cases,
我们得谈谈他们这样我们就能避开他们了
we gotta talk about them so
that we can avoid them.